Guide to the Wells Fargo Steinbeck Collection, 1892-1981
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4. John Steinbeck Letters to Family, 1910-1968
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1926 Fall] (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA [1926] Nov. 1 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1926 Nov. 11 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1926 Nov. 18 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - ALS, 4 pp. (1 folded leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1926 Nov. 22 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA [1926 Nov. 27] (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1926 Dec.] (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - TL, 3 pp. (2 leaves)
  - [John Steinbeck], Tahoe, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA n.d. [1926 Dec. 14] (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - TL (fragment), 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Mar. 19 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Mar. 22 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Mar. 29 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Apr. 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Apr. 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Apr.] (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Apr. 12 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 2 p.. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Apr.] (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Apr.] (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Apr. 30 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tallac, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tallac, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tallac, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tallac, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Mother [Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA n.d. [1927 June] (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 July 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Aug. 16 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Aug. 24 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Sept. 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Sept. 15 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Sept. 21 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA [1927] Oct. 17 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Oct. 25 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - TL (with holographic note verso), 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Fall] (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Nov. 24] (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Dec. 6 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1927 Dec. 10 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Dec.] (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Everybody, n.p. [Salinas, CA] 1927 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - ALS, 3 pp. (2 leaves) + 2 envelopes
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Mother [Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1927 Dec.] (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Camp Richardson, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] 1927 Dec. 23 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] 1927 Dec. 27 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Camp Richardson, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] 1927 Dec. 31 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tahoe, [CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 3 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 7 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1928 Jan.] (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 14 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 21 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1928 Jan.] (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 28 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tahoe, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 31 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Jan. 31 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - TLS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA [1928] Feb. 4 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Feb 7 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Feb. 11 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Feb. 14 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Feb. 21 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Mar. 24 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Mar. 31 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA n.d. [1928 Apr.] (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Tahoe, CA], to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], n.p. [Salinas, CA] n.d. [1928 Apr.] (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Apr. 7 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Apr. 14 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Dad [John Ernst Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Apr. 17 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Apr 21 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Camp Richardson, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA [1928] Apr. 24 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tahoe, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Tahoe, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1928 Sept. 11 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Eagle Rock, CA, to Folks [John Ernst and Olive Hamilton Steinbeck], Salinas, CA 1930 Jan. 18 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - TL (with holographic note), 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], Pacific Grove, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1936 Jan. 30 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Gatos, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1939 July 14 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Gatos, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1939 Aug. 30 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Gatos, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1939 Sept. 17 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Gatos, CA, to Joe [Hamilton], Washington, DC 1939 Oct. 23 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - TLS, 3 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Gatos, CA, to Joe and Gussie [Hamilton], Washington, DC 1940 July 9 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Gatos, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1940 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - TPC
  - [John Steinbeck], Pacific Grove, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1941 July 13 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1941 Nov. 21 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Atlanta, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1942] Jan. 6 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1942 Jan. 18 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - ALS, 3 pp. (1 folded leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1942 Mar. 2 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Palisades, NY, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1942 Apr. 3 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Albuquerque, NM, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1942 June (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Palisades, NY, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1942] June 24 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Palisades, NY, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1942] July 25 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - AL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Palisades, NY, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1942 Aug. 10 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Sherman Oaks, CA, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1942 Sept.] (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Sherman Oaks, CA, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1942 Dec.] (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Sherman Oaks, CA, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1942 Dec.] (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Van Nuys, CA, to Mrs. J.R. [Gussie] Hamilton, Chicago 1943 Jan. 3 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - telegram
  - [John Steinbeck], Van Nuys, CA, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1943 Jan. 4 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Los Angeles, CA, to Aunt Gussie [Hamilton], Chicago 1943 Jan. 4 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Van Nuys, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1943 Jan. [6] (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Somewhere in New Mexico [Albuquerque, NM] to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1943 Jan. 20 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Thursday [1943 Feb. 25] (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA n.d. [1943 Mar.] (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Sunday [1943 May 16] (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Wednesday [1943 Nov. 3] (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA n.d. [1943 Dec. 4] (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and all, Watsonville, CA 1943 Dec. 26 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1943 Dec. 28 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] [1944] Apr. 3 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1944 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Thursday [1944 July 27] (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Mrs. C.J. [Esther] Rodgers, n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1944 Aug. 3 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - telegram
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1944 Aug. 8 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] Saturday [1944 Aug. 12?] (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1944 July 5 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1946 Jan. 17 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 Apr. 25 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1946 May (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - telegram
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 June 14 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Mary Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 July 16 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], 175 E. 78th, [New York], to Esther [Rodgers] and all, n.p. [Watsonville, CA] [1946] July 17 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1946 Aug.] (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 Aug. 21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1946 Sept.] (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - TL, 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 Sept. 24 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1946 Oct. 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1946 Oct. 10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Coney Island, NY, to All, n.p. n.d. [1946 Oct?] (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Mrs. C.J. [Esther] Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 Oct. 17 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - telegram
  - [John Steinbeck], aboard Swedish American Line, S.S. Drottningholm, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1946] Oct. 19 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Stockholm, Sweden], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA n.d. [1946 Fall] (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1946 Dec. 4 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and all the family, Watsonville, CA 1946 Dec. 19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and all, n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1946 Dec.] (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] Monday [1947 Feb.] (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Mrs. C.J. [Esther] Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 Apr. 3 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 Apr. 21 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 May 27 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Paris, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 July 12 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 Nov. 10 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - TL, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1947 Dec. 22 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and all, Watsonville, CA Sunday [1947 Dec. 29] (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1948 Mar. 20 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1948 Apr. 24 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1948 May 1 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1948 July 14 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] [1948] Aug. 10 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to [Esther Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA]. n.d. [1950 Feb.] (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - AN
  - [John Steinbeck], Malibu, CA, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] n.d. [1949 Sept.] (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Malibu, CA, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1949 Sept. 28 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] Thursday [1949 Dec.] (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and all family, n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] 1949 Dec. 26 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] 1950 Jan. 4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - ALS, 4 pp. (2 leaves)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1950 Jan. 6 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1950 Jan. 9 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - ALS, 1p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] [1950] Jan. 19 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] [1950] Feb. 11 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1950 Feb. 16 (Box 6, Folder 19)